<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Repositories for Android in Github</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_add_favourite">Add to Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="action_play_next">Share</string>
    <string name="backdrop_title">LOVE MUSIC</string>
    <string name="backdrop_subtitle">This season top 20 albums</string>
    <string name="title_activity_listitems">listitems</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation">navigation</string>
    <string name="banner_customListview">ca-app-pub-8861549201942078/5174601950</string>
    <string name="banner_ExpandableListView">ca-app-pub-8861549201942078/3566485748</string>
    <string name="banner_Bookmarks">ca-app-pub-8861549201942078/6365352551</string>
    <string name="banner_OpenGithubLink">ca-app-pub-8861549201942078/3743058646</string>
    <string name="banner_FileManager">ca-app-pub-8861549201942078/1480212606</string>
    <string name="interstitial_full_screen">ca-app-pub-8861549201942078/7693433013</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Bookmarks">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_File_Manager">File Manager</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Clear_App_Data">Clear App Data</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_More_Apps_By_Developer">More Apps By Developer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Share_this_App">Share this App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Rate_App">Rate this App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_About">About</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Privacy_Policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Wallistract">Wallistract-HD Wallpapers</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Facebook">Facebook Video Downloader</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Ads_Free_Facebook">(Ads Free)Facebook Video Downloader Pro</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_Raja_Mantri_Chor_Sipahi">Raja Mantri Chor Sipahi</string>
    <string name="repositories">repositories</string>
    <string name="All_Rights_Reserved">All Rights Reserved</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Browse">Browse between 500+ repositories divided into various categories!</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Search">Search for a particular category!</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Bookmark">Bookmark and view your favourite repostories!</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Download">Download and unzip to see files of repositories!</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Share">Liked any repository?Just Share them with your colleagues/friends!</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Title_Share">Share</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Title_Download">Download</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Title_Bookmark">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Title_Search">Search</string>
    <string name="Onboarding_Title_Browse">Browse</string>
    <string name="_repository_Bookmarked_"> repository Bookmarked !</string>
    <string name="Removed_from_Bookmarks"> repository Removed from Bookmarks !</string>


    <string name="description_1">Collect and classify android open source projects</string>
    <string name="description_2">A library to bring fully animated Material Design components to pre-Lolipop Android</string>
    <string name="description_3">Demos the new Android Design library.</string>
    <string name="description_4">This is a library with components of Android L to you use in android 2.2</string>
    <string name="description_5">Android Material Design Theme UI and Tool Library. Support: 4.0.3~N</string>
    <string name="description_6">A simple app to showcase Androids Material Design and some of the cool new cool stuff in Android Lollipop. RecyclerView, CardView, ActionBarDrawerToggle, DrawerLayout, Animations, Android Compat Design, Toolbar</string>
    <string name="description_7">Material Design implementation for Android 2.3+. Shadows, ripples, vectors, fonts, animations, widgets, rounded corners and more.</string>
    <string name="description_8">A demo of the Android Material Design Support libraries</string>
    <string name="description_9">Just Sample how to use the android design support lib</string>
    <string name="description_10">Android Design Support Library Demo</string>
    <string name="description_11">MaterialUp Android App</string>
    <string name="description_12">A simple backward-compatible implementation of a Material Design Preference aka settings item</string>
    <string name="description_13">This is a State of the Art Android Material Design template. You can use this project as a template for upcoming App projects. Just clone the project, change package name and make all necessary customzations.</string>
    <string name="description_14">[Deprecated] Little bites of Material Design</string>
    <string name="description_15">Implementation of ImageView for Android that supports zooming, by various touch gestures.</string>
    <string name="description_16">Support for scalable vector graphics in Android</string>
    <string name="description_17">Custom ImageView for moving image around the screen (Android)</string>
    <string name="description_18">A circular ImageView for Android</string>
    <string name="description_19">Custom view for circular images in Android while maintaining the best draw performance</string>
    <string name="description_20">Create circular ImageView in Android in the simplest way possible.</string>
    <string name="description_21">Android ImageView that supports different radii on each corner</string>
    <string name="description_22">Custom shaped android imageview components</string>
    <string name="description_23">An Android view for displaying repeated continuous side scrolling images. This can be used to create a parallax animation effect.</string>
    <string name="description_24">Adds touch functionality to Android ImageView.</string>
    <string name="description_25">A custom widget for Android, which uesd for showing grid pictures</string>
    <string name="description_26">Implements pinch-zoom, rotate, pan as an ImageView for Android 2.1+</string>
    <string name="description_27">Android ImageViews animated by Ken Burns Effect</string>
    <string name="description_28">An amazing and convenient Android image slider.</string>
    <string name="description_29">Views and Drawable for displaying animated GIFs on Android</string>
    <string name="description_30">Library for playing gifs on Android</string>
    <string name="description_31">Android ImageView that handles animated GIF images</string>
    <string name="description_32">TileView is a subclass of android.view.ViewGroup that asynchronously displays tile-based images, with pan and zoom functionality, and support for features like markers, hotspots, paths, multiple levels of detail, and arbitrary coordinate systems.</string>
    <string name="description_33">ImageView with a tag on android</string>
    <string name="description_34">Some beautiful android loading drawable, can be combined with any view as the LoadingView or the ProgressBar. Besides, some Drawable can customize the loading progress too.</string>
    <string name="description_35">Visual back-port of the rotating drawer-to-arrow drawable from Android L</string>
    <string name="description_36">Customizable Android full screen image viewer for Fresco library supporting\'pinch to zoom\' and \'swipe to dismiss\' gestures</string>
    <string name="description_37">edit personal information which enables users to drag and rank image order</string>
    <string name="description_38">Android widget for gallery, using viewpager. Allow pinch zoom and drag for images by url</string>
    <string name="description_39">A Java Application to create appropriate Drawable resources for your Android application</string>
    <string name="description_40">Experience very good Android picture gesture control.</string>
    <string name="description_41">Android widget for cropping and rotating an image.</string>
    <string name="description_42">Android library project for cropping images</string>
    <string name="description_43">Ucrop -Image Cropping Library for Android </string>
    <string name="description_44">Image Cropping Library for Android, optimized for Camera / Gallery.</string>
    <string name="description_45">Android image cropping library</string>
    <string name="description_46">A simple image cropping library for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_47">CropImage Activity from Gallery.apk packaged as a reusable Android library (4.0 and up).</string>
    <string name="description_48">Widget allows you crop from whatever side in an ImageView. Currently Android only supports centerCrop type of cropping</string>
    <string name="description_49">The Ultimate Approach to crop photos on android devices, especially for large size photos. This way can help you avoid OOM(OutOfMemory) exception.</string>
    <string name="description_50">Android StackBlur is a library that can perform a blurry effect on a Bitmap based on a gradient or radius, and return the result. The library is based on the code of Mario Klingemann.</string>
    <string name="description_51">Blurry is an easy blur library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_52">Sample to show how to implement blur graphical tricks</string>
    <string name="description_53">Dynamic iOS-like blur of underlying Views for Android</string>
    <string name="description_54">Android blurring image(bitmap) by java and jni.</string>
    <string name="description_55">A realtime blurring overlay for Android (like iOS UIVisualEffectView)</string>
    <string name="description_56">Dynamic blur of image views for Android</string>
    <string name="description_57">AndroidPhotoFilters aims to provide fast, powerful and flexible image processing instrument for creating awesome effects on any image media.</string>
    <string name="description_58">Android ImageView widget with zoom and pan capabilities</string>
    <string name="description_59">Realtime camera filters for android.</string>
    <string name="description_60">Nice filter image library</string>
    <string name="description_61">AndroidImageEdit Android device graphics editing open source control, support for custom map image filter image rotation image clip text texture operation</string>
    <string name="description_62">A small android library to transition between a circular ImageView from one Activity to a rectangular ImageView in the launched Activity.</string>
    <string name="description_63">A powerful image downloading and caching library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_64">An Android transformation library providing a variety of image transformations for Picasso</string>
    <string name="description_65">An Android image transformation library providing cropping above Face Detection (Face Centering) for Picasso.</string>
    <string name="description_66">An image loading and caching library for Android focused on smooth scrolling</string>
    <string name="description_67">An Android transformation library providing a variety of image transformations for Glide.</string>
    <string name="description_68">Android Lollipop Palette is now easy to use with Glide</string>
    <string name="description_69">An Android library for managing images and the memory they use.</string>
    <string name="description_70">An Android image processor library providing a variety of image transformations for Fresco.</string>
    <string name="description_71">Powerful and flexible library for loading, caching and displaying images on Android.</string>
    <string name="description_72">Android Asynchronous Networking and Image Loading</string>
    <string name="description_73">Android ImageView replacement which allows image loading from URLs or contact address book, with caching</string>
    <string name="description_74">Lazy load of images in Android</string>
    <string name="description_75">Android library that sets an ImageView\'s contents from a url. Manages image downloading, caching, and makes your coffee too.</string>
    <string name="description_76">Library for async image loading and caching on Android</string>
    <string name="description_77">An Android library allowing images to exhibit a parallax effect that reacts to the device\'s tilt</string>
    <string name="description_78">Android Studio plugin which automatically generates drawable selectors from appropriately named resources.</string>
    <string name="description_79">An android image compression library.</string>
    <string name="description_80">An Advanced Compress Image Library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_81">Select images from Android devices made easy :-) Start Activity PhotoSelectorActivity, this is the main entry point</string>
    <string name="description_82">Adds an option to IntelliJ to import drawables in different resolutions from AndroidIcons, own drawable repos and scale a certain image down/up to the defined resolutions.</string>
    <string name="description_83">An Easy Image/Video Chooser Library for your Android Apps</string>
    <string name="description_84">Simple Android Album</string>
    <string name="description_85">Android picture selection, preview, Jiugongge picture control, drag and drop image control</string>
    <string name="description_86">Paging indicator widgets compatible with the ViewPager from the Android Support Library and ActionBarSherlock.</string>
    <string name="description_87">Android auto scroll viewpager or viewpager in viewpager</string>
    <string name="description_88">Library containing common animations needed for transforming ViewPager scrolling for Android v13+.</string>
    <string name="description_89">NewsStand Application for Android\'s view of play, such as a pager function that implements the code.</string>
    <string name="description_90">[DEPRECATED] Implementation of the compatibility library ViewPager class that supports paging both vertically and horizontally.</string>
    <string name="description_91">Android pager-style wizard flow sample code</string>
    <string name="description_92">Vertically ViewPager and vertically transformer for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_93">Augment Android\'s ViewPager with wrap-around functionality.</string>
    <string name="description_94">An easy to use ViewPager that adds an awesome set of custom swiping animations.</string>
    <string name="description_95">An android ViewPager extension allowing infinite scrolling</string>
    <string name="description_96">A rubber indicator</string>
    <string name="description_97">An page indicator for Android ViewPager</string>
    <string name="description_98">vertical slide to switch to the next fragment page, looks like vertical viewpager</string>
    <string name="description_99">An ViewPager based Android Banner that supports auto scrolling and decent animation</string>
    <string name="description_100">viewpager with parallax pages, together with vertical sliding (or click) and activity transition</string>
    <string name="description_101">[DEPRECATED] Action bar implementation which uses the native action bar on Android 4.0+ and a custom implementation on pre-4.0 through a single API and theme</string>
    <string name="description_102">DEPRECATED Android Action Bar Implementation</string>
    <string name="description_103">Android library implementing a fading effect for the action bar, similar to the one found in the Play Music app</string>
    <string name="description_104">Android - a library that adds a glass-like effect to the action bar.</string>
    <string name="description_105">An bottom navigation bar for Android</string>
    <string name="description_106">Android Sample Project with Material Design and Toolbar.</string>
    <string name="description_107">Android - An action bar item which acts both as a refresh button and as a progress indicator</string>
    <string name="description_108">Android ListView with drag and drop reordering.</string>
    <string name="description_109">Easy to use ListView with pinned sections for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_110">An android library for section headers that stick to the top</string>
    <string name="description_111">A ListView with pinned section headers for Android</string>
    <string name="description_112">iPhone like fast scroll ListView on Android</string>
    <string name="description_113">Horizontal list view for Android which allows variable items widths</string>
    <string name="description_114">A Horizontal ListView for Android http://www.dev-smart.com/archives/34</string>
    <string name="description_115">ListView supports pull refresh and pull up to load more feature.</string>
    <string name="description_116">An Android custom ListView with pull to zoom-in and parallax effect header like Path App.</string>
    <string name="description_117">Android boosted ListView supporting paginated header with a new material page indicator.</string>
    <string name="description_118">HorizontalListView is an Android ListView widget which scrolls in a horizontal manner (in contrast with the SDK-provided ListView which scrolls vertically).</string>
    <string name="description_119">A generic, customizable, open source Android ListView implementation that has\'Pull to Refresh\' functionality.</string>
    <string name="description_120">Android library to display a ListView whose cells are not rigid but flabby and react to ListView scroll.</string>
    <string name="description_121">A smooth and beautiful Android drop-down refreshes with more list components loaded.</string>
    <string name="description_122">Android library that allows you to bind a LinearLayout with a ListAdapter.</string>
    <string name="description_123">Android - A ListView adapter with support for multiple choice modal selection</string>
    <string name="description_124">An Android multi column list view like Pinterest.</string>
    <string name="description_125">A library for showing different types of layouts when a list view is empty</string>
    <string name="description_126">A better ExpandableListView, with animated expandable views for each list item</string>
    <string name="description_127">An Android staggered grid view which supports multiple columns with rows of varying sizes.</string>
    <string name="description_128">A modified version of Android\'s experimental StaggeredGridView. Includes own OnItemClickListener and OnItemLongClickListener, selector, and fixed position restore.</string>
    <string name="description_129">A GridView which can addHeaderView and addFooterView</string>
    <string name="description_130">Android ListView that mimics a GridView with asymmetric items. Supports items with row span and column span</string>
    <string name="description_131">A drag-and-drop scrolling grid view for Android</string>
    <string name="description_132">Drag and drop GridView for Android</string>
    <string name="description_133">An Android GridView that can be configured to scroll horizontally or vertically</string>
    <string name="description_134">Proof of concept Android WebView implementation based on Chromium code</string>
    <string name="description_135">chrome browser of android version from chromium open project</string>
    <string name="description_136">A plugin system that runs like a browser, but instead of load web pages, it load apk plugins which runs natively on Android system.</string>
    <string name="description_137">Beautiful and customizable Android Activity that shows web pages within an app.</string>
    <string name="description_138">Android\'s WebView and WebChromeClient class extensions that enable fully working HTML5 video support</string>
    <string name="description_139">Slide is an open sourced, ad free Reddit browser for Android https://reddit.com/r/slideforreddit</string>
    <string name="description_140">A nice spinner for Android</string>
    <string name="description_141">DropDownMenu for Android,Filter the list based on multiple condition.</string>
    <string name="description_142">Wheel-like spinner widget for Android</string>
    <string name="description_143">A simple yet-powerful and fully customizable Android drop-down menu. It supports Text with/without Icons, Separators, and even fully customized views.</string>
    <string name="description_144">Android-ScrollBarPanel allows to attach a View to a scroll indicator like it\'s done in Path 2.0</string>
    <string name="description_145">An Android custom ListView and ScrollView with pull to zoom-in.</string>
    <string name="description_146">Android library to observe scroll events on scrollable views.</string>
    <string name="description_147">A small android library for tagging views inside a ScrollView as \'sticky\' making them stick to the top of the scroll container until a new sticky view comes and takes it\'s place</string>
    <string name="description_148">1. follow the Sina microblogging Android client personal center ScrollView, pull back the background stretch rebound effect. 2.ScrollView imitation IOS rebound effect.</string>
    <string name="description_149">Android: iOS-like over-scrolling effect applicable over almost all scrollable Android views.</string>
    <string name="description_150">Android scrollable tabs</string>
    <string name="description_151">Microlibrary for implementing infinite scroll on Android</string>
    <string name="description_152">This is a very simple library for Android that allows you to stick an header to a scrollable view and easily apply animation to it</string>
    <string name="description_153">An Android library that allows you to easily create applications with slide-in menus. You may use it in your Android apps provided that you cite this project and include the license in your app. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="description_154">[UNMAINTAINED] An implemention of Filter Menu concept for android</string>
    <string name="description_155">Parallax ScrollView and ListView for Android</string>
    <string name="description_156">Layered parallax effect to any Android views</string>
    <string name="description_157">Add some depth to your Android scrolling.</string>
    <string name="description_158">Aware of the Android client launch page parallax animation effects</string>
    <string name="description_159">Parallax everywhere is a library with alternative android widgets with parallax effects.</string>
    <string name="description_160">A pager for Android with parallax effect</string>
    <string name="description_161">A Android ListView Demo with a parallax effect header like Path.</string>
    <string name="description_162">Cute view animation collection.</string>
    <string name="description_163">[DEPRECATED] An Android library which allows developers to easily add animations to ListView items</string>
    <string name="description_164">A library that gives depth to Views.</string>
    <string name="description_165">An elegant way to show your menu or messages.</string>
    <string name="description_166">A RecyclerView(advanced and flexible version of ListView in Android) with refreshing,loading more,animation and many other features.</string>
    <string name="description_167">RecyclerView extension library which provides advanced features. (ex. Google\'s Inbox app like swiping, Play Music app like drag and drop sorting)</string>
    <string name="description_168">Android Library to provide swipe, click and other functionality to RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_169">Android RecyclerView Demo</string>
    <string name="description_170">Android library providing simple way to control divider items (ItemDecoration) of RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_171">A pull to refresh layout for android, the RecyclerRefreshLayout is based on the SwipeRefreshLayout. support all the views, highly customizable, code simplicity, etc</string>
    <string name="description_172">Full aspect ratio grid LayoutManager for Android\'s RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_173">Basic example of using ItemTouchHelper to add drag &amp; drop and swipe-to-dismiss to RecyclerView.</string>
    <string name="description_174">Epoxy is an Android library for building complex screens in a RecyclerView https://goo.gl/eIK82p</string>
    <string name="description_175">Android Carousel LayoutManager for RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_176">An Android library which provides simple Item animations to RecyclerView items</string>
    <string name="description_177">An Android Animation library which easily add itemanimator to RecyclerView items.</string>
    <string name="description_178">An adapter which could be used to achieve a parallax effect on RecyclerView.</string>
    <string name="description_179">A simple FastScroller for Android\'s RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_180">Android library for material scrolling techniques.</string>
    <string name="description_181">Super fast and easy way to create header for Android RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_182">Adapter and LayoutManager for Android RecyclerView which enables sticky header positioning.</string>
    <string name="description_183">[UNMAINTAINED] Sticky Headers decorator for Android\'s RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_184">DEPRECATED. Android library that integrate sticky section headers in your RecyclerView</string>
    <string name="description_185">Easy async loading for Android\'s ListView/GridView</string>
    <string name="description_186">Sample of a Cube App</string>
    <string name="description_187">A library that easily allows you to mask layouts/viewgroups</string>
    <string name="description_188">An Android library to retrofit multiple item view types</string>
    <string name="description_189">A beautiful ripple animation for your app</string>
    <string name="description_190">View that imitates Ripple Effect on click which was introduced in Android L (for Android 2.3+)</string>
    <string name="description_191">Implementation of Ripple effect from Material Design for Android API 9+</string>
    <string name="description_192">An easy, flexible way to add a shimmering effect to any view in an Android app.</string>
    <string name="description_193">A motion-driven animation framework for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_194">Android like button with delightful star animation inspired by Twitter\'s heart.</string>
    <string name="description_195">Android Transition animations explanation with examples.</string>
    <string name="description_196">A fluent Android animation library</string>
    <string name="description_197">Android library to control Transition animates. A simple way to create a interactive animation.</string>
    <string name="description_198">Android animation when entering new screen.</string>
    <string name="description_199">Sample material transition animations for Android</string>
    <string name="description_200">BaseAnimation network Android animation set, custom controls, nearly 200 kinds of source code！</string>
    <string name="description_201">Twenty-eight different easing animation interpolators for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_202">Thirty different easing animation interpolators for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_203">Android Animation Easing Functions. Let\'s make animation more real!</string>
    <string name="description_204">An Android particle system library for displaying confetti!</string>
    <string name="description_205">A Particle System for standard Android UI</string>
    <string name="description_206">Android\'s animated fingerprint icon provided in a simple, standalone library.</string>
    <string name="description_207">FPSAnimator is very easy animation library for Android TextureView and SurfaceView.</string>
    <string name="description_208">Allows the easy creation of animated transition effects when the state of Android UI has changed</string>
    <string name="description_209">Set of samples of views with slick interaction patterns and animations</string>
    <string name="description_210">A component for flip animation on Android, which is similar to the effect in Flipboard iPhone/Android</string>
    <string name="description_211">Pulse animation for Android</string>
    <string name="description_212">This is a library that contains practical animations: Rotation, Flip, Horizontal and Vertical Shake, Pulse.</string>
    <string name="description_213">An example application for creating page curl/flip effect on Android using OpenGL ES.</string>
    <string name="description_214">This component implements transition animation to crumble view into tiny pieces.</string>
    <string name="description_215">Animated SVG Drawing for Android</string>
    <string name="description_216">greenDAO is a light &amp; fast ORM solution for Android that maps objects to SQLite databases.</string>
    <string name="description_217">A blazing fast, powerful, and very simple ORM android database library that writes database code for you.</string>
    <string name="description_218">ORMLite Android functionality used in conjunction with ormlite-core</string>
    <string name="description_219">An Android library that makes developers use SQLite database extremely easy.</string>
    <string name="description_220">An Android helper class to manage database creation and version management using an application\'s raw asset files</string>
    <string name="description_221">SquiDB is a SQLite database library for Android and iOS</string>
    <string name="description_222">Android SQLite API based on SQLCipher</string>
    <string name="description_223">Insanely easy way to work with Android Database.</string>
    <string name="description_224">Fast and simple data storage library for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_225">Android library for viewing and sharing in app databases.</string>
    <string name="description_226">An Android Library for data management.</string>
    <string name="description_227">Lightweight, embedded, syncable NoSQL database engine for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_228">Android integration of multiple icon providers such as FontAwesome, Entypo, Typicons.</string>
    <string name="description_229">Over 1600 customizable icons for Android including 750+ Google Material Design icons, 25 ready-made social badges, and more!</string>
    <string name="description_230">Android-Iconics - Use any icon font, or vector (.svg) as drawable in your application.</string>
    <string name="description_231">Bootstrap style widgets for Android, with Glyph Icons</string>
    <string name="description_232">A template/bootstrap/boilerplate application that includes tons of great open source tools and frameworks.</string>
    <string name="description_233">A bootstrap project for TDD Android.</string>
    <string name="description_234">A beautiful set of predefined colors and a set of color methods to make your Android development life easier.</string>
    <string name="description_235">iTunes 11-style color matching code for Android</string>
    <string name="description_236">An Android Holo themed colorpicker designed by Marie Schweiz</string>
    <string name="description_237">A dynamic colouring library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_238">GreenDroid is a development library for the Android platform. It makes UI developments easier and consistent through your applications</string>
    <string name="description_239">Dissect layout traversals on Android</string>
    <string name="description_240">Define and render UI specs on top of your Android UI</string>
    <string name="description_241">Default colors and dimens per Material Design guidelines and Android Design guidelines inside one library.</string>
    <string name="description_242">Android view with both path from constructed path or from svg.</string>
    <string name="description_243">A sample Android application that demonstrates how to implement various visual effects.</string>
    <string name="description_244">This project includes sample applications that demonstrate different features of the Android Framework and Support Library.It is actively managed by the Android Framework Team.</string>
    <string name="description_245">Library and example project on how to use the UITableView component</string>
    <string name="description_246">iOS UIActionSheet for Android</string>
    <string name="description_247">Sample project created to show some of the best Android practices to work in the Android UI Layer.</string>
    <string name="description_248">Android library for managing and applying multiple themes and custom theme modification</string>
    <string name="description_249">Android related examples</string>
    <string name="description_250">Blog Demo Storage</string>
    <string name="description_251">This is a collection of Android Apps which are open source.</string>
    <string name="description_252">Barcode Scanner Libraries for Android</string>
    <string name="description_253">Android common lib demo, include ImageCache, HttpCache, DropDownListView, DownloadManager, install apk silent and so on, you can find description</string>
    <string name="description_254">A Full-Stack mobile app, including Android &amp; Server, Simple-Poem 简诗. You can write poem in graceful &amp; traditional Chinese style.</string>
    <string name="description_255">A material-design Hacker News Android reader</string>
    <string name="description_256">ChatSecure for Android (previously known as Gibberbot) is a secure messaging app built on open standards like XMPP/Jabber and OTR encryption:</string>
    <string name="description_257">A simple chat demo for socket.io and Androids</string>
    <string name="description_258">[Deprecated] Simple Facebook SDK for Android</string>
    <string name="description_259">A messaging library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_260">Tweet Lanes for Android</string>
    <string name="description_261">Simple habit tracker for Android</string>
    <string name="description_262">App for Android phones that counts your steps.</string>
    <string name="description_263">Lightweight pedometer app for Android using the hardware step sensor</string>
    <string name="description_264">the source code in research art of android development</string>
    <string name="description_265">Android Next public component library</string>
    <string name="description_266">wall:splash is a free open source android client for the awesome unsplash.com service (Free (do whatever you want) high-resolution photos)</string>
    <string name="description_267">A project which demonstrate how to develop a custom client on android for dribbble.com</string>
    <string name="description_268">An android feed reader application which fetch data with selector and regular expression.</string>
    <string name="description_269">GitHub Android application</string>
    <string name="description_270">ECShop-based mobile phone mall client</string>
    <string name="description_271">WordPress for Android</string>
    <string name="description_272">Android view for displaying PDFs rendered with PdfiumAndroid</string>
    <string name="description_273">RSVP reader for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_274">Pdf Viewer library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_275">Experimental app for optical character recognition on Android</string>
    <string name="description_276">card.io provides fast, easy credit card scanning in mobile apps</string>
    <string name="description_277">Android Studio Plugin, Translate English to Chinese. Android Studio translation plug-in, you can translate English into Chinese.</string>
    <string name="description_278">Official Todo.txt Android app for managing your todo.txt file stored in Dropbox</string>
    <string name="description_279">Extensive Open-Source Guides for Android Developers</string>
    <string name="description_280">Training course repository for android app development</string>
    <string name="description_281">Full tutorial in step by step is available at http://inthecheesefactory.com/blog/android-design-support-library-codelab</string>
    <string name="description_282">Android Interview Review</string>
    <string name="description_283">Kick-starts Android application development.</string>
    <string name="description_284">Android System UI Training Code</string>
    <string name="description_285">Fast Android Development. Easy maintainance. http://androidannotations.org</string>
    <string name="description_286">The top Internet companies android interview questions and answers</string>
    <string name="description_287">The Best Android  Training Course by Coursera</string>
    <string name="description_288">Source Code to _The Busy Coder\'s Guide To Advanced Android Development_ http://commonsware.com/AdvAndroid/</string>
    <string name="description_289">Source Code to _The Busy Coder\'s Guide To Android Development_ http://commonsware.com/Android/</string>
    <string name="description_290">Source code of the book - Android Heroes</string>
    <string name="description_291">Source code related to the posts in the blog http://www.survivingwithandroid.com</string>
    <string name="description_292">A collection of quickstart samples demonstrating the Google APIs for Android and iOS https://developers.google.com</string>
    <string name="description_293">A simple, annotation-based library for making deep link handling better on Android http://nerds.airbnb.com/deeplinkdispa…</string>
    <string name="description_294">Examples of Android applications http://www.novoda.com/blog</string>
    <string name="description_295">source code in blog~</string>
    <string name="description_296">Collection of source codes, utilities, templates and snippets for Android development.</string>
    <string name="description_297">Google Play game services - Android samples</string>
    <string name="description_298">Implementation of Play Services Core package</string>
    <string name="description_299">Native Android sample of all samples for beginners and experienced, 14+, with focus on lollipop and Material</string>
    <string name="description_300">Collected code examples from the O\'Reilly Android Cookbook. See README below! http://androidcookbook.com/</string>
    <string name="description_301">Some Android learning materials, hoping to help you learn Android development.</string>
    <string name="description_302">Do\'s and Don\'ts for Android development, by Futurice developers</string>
    <string name="description_303">Every Android Studio Tip posted by Phillipe Breault</string>
    <string name="description_304">List of Tips for Awesome AN Android.</string>
    <string name="description_305">A collection of tips in Android developing. Android development summary.</string>
    <string name="description_306">Android App Common Tasks library is developed to reduce efforts to achieve common tasks of the android apps quickly.</string>
    <string name="description_307">The Google I/O 2016 Android App</string>
    <string name="description_308">Sample android project using Gradle, with basic quality tools set up.</string>
    <string name="description_309">Android application powering the mirror in my house</string>
    <string name="description_310">less code, more efficient for android</string>
    <string name="description_311">Spring for Android Sample Applications</string>
    <string name="description_312">AndroidFire, a news reader App framework, based on Material Design + MVP + RxJava + Retrofit + Glide, basically covers the current Android-side development of the most commonly used mainstream framework, based on this framework can quickly develop an app</string>
    <string name="description_313">Github client for Android</string>
    <string name="description_314">Analysis implementation of android open source project</string>
    <string name="description_315">This sample shows how to implement an audio media app that works across multiple form factors and provide a consistent user experience on Android phones, tablets, Auto, Wear and Cast devices</string>
    <string name="description_316">An extensible media player for Android</string>
    <string name="description_317">A free, powerful and elegant music player for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_318">A solution for streaming H.264, H.263, AMR, AAC using RTP on Android</string>
    <string name="description_319">Android custom view and progress for music player</string>
    <string name="description_320">Custom android music player view.</string>
    <string name="description_321">DMPLayer is an Android music player prototype</string>
    <string name="description_322">Tomahawk\'s Android Music Player</string>
    <string name="description_323">A stylish music player for android device 16+</string>
    <string name="description_324">Beautiful Circular Progress Bar with album art for android</string>
    <string name="description_325">Horizon - Simple visual equaliser for Android</string>
    <string name="description_326">Live Audio Equalizer with wave effect.</string>
    <string name="description_327">Android app that takes the audio output of the device and uses it to create visuals that go along with the sounds.</string>
    <string name="description_328">Displays the audio spectrum</string>
    <string name="description_329">Takes the input from the Android MediaPlayer and displays visualizations, like in iTunes or WinAmp.</string>
    <string name="description_330">Awesome Audio Widget for any Android Music App.</string>
    <string name="description_331">Shows a graphic representation of the sounds captured by the microphone on Android</string>
    <string name="description_332">Android VideoPlayer MediaPlayer VideoView MediaView Float View And Fullscreen</string>
    <string name="description_333">This is a project designed to help controlling Android MediaPlayer class.</string>
    <string name="description_334">Android video recording, imitating micro-view, support press to record, lift pause. The progress bar breakpoint is displayed.</string>
    <string name="description_335">Android Video Player , Like NetEaseNews Video Player.</string>
    <string name="description_336">An Android ExoPlayer wrapper to simplify Audio and Video implementations</string>
    <string name="description_337">Android Texture VideoView having a variety of scale types like the scale types of ImageView such as fitCenter, centerCrop, centerTopCrop and more.</string>
    <string name="description_338">Video playback on Android, made easy, wrapping around the stock MediaPlayer API.</string>
    <string name="description_339">Cache support for any video player with help of single line</string>
    <string name="description_340">Integrated android streaming media processing of the mainstream framework, vitamio, ijkplayer and so on.</string>
    <string name="description_341">Keep track of your favorite TV shows and movies on your Android devices.</string>
    <string name="description_342">Android Multi channel package tool (Android multi channel package tool)</string>
    <string name="description_343">One of the most difficult APIs on Android, made easy in a small library.</string>
    <string name="description_344">Real-time Filter Camera&amp;VideoRecorder And ImageEditor With Face Beauty For Android</string>
    <string name="description_345">Powerful custom Android Camera with granular control over the video quality and filesize, restricting recordings to landscape only.</string>
    <string name="description_346">A powerful and funny android app. that streams the camera and microphone of your phone to your browser or to VLC</string>
    <string name="description_347">This sample demonstrates how to use basic functionalities of Camera2 API.</string>
    <string name="description_348">Simple camera module for android applications.</string>
    <string name="description_349">Wrapper around the android Camera class that simplifies its usage</string>
    <string name="description_350">Open camera project - multi-functional camera application for android.</string>
    <string name="description_351">Android Camera API, Made Better. Again.</string>
    <string name="description_352">Make a cool intro for your Android app.</string>
    <string name="description_353">Android Library for making animated tutorials inside your app.</string>
    <string name="description_354">PaperOnboarding is a material design slider</string>
    <string name="description_355">A customizable welcome screen</string>
    <string name="description_356">Welcome Coordinator for Android</string>
    <string name="description_357">Create an awesome About Page for your Android App in 2 minutes</string>
    <string name="description_358">A small Android library to manage one-off operations.</string>
    <string name="description_359">LeafPic is an ad-free, open-source and material-designed android gallery alternative</string>
    <string name="description_360">Spotlight is an Android library used to onboard users by showcasing specific features in the app.</string>
    <string name="description_361">Rotate image controls for Android, with unlimited loops and a variety of themes, with the flexibility to set up rotation styles, animations, carousels, and switch times, positions, image loading frames, and more!</string>
    <string name="description_362">Android Library to build a UI Card</string>
    <string name="description_363">An Android library aimed to get the beautiful CardViews that Google shows at its official design specifications</string>
    <string name="description_364">enable users to slide card to the left or right smoothly and continuously</string>
    <string name="description_365">Based on https://github.com/xmuSistone/android-card-slide-panel.git</string>
    <string name="description_366">Free time to develop an App, unofficial knowledge column App, which all the content from the know, the contents of the copyright is also know almost.</string>
    <string name="description_367">Android optimized event bus that simplifies communication between Activities, Fragments, Threads, Services, etc. Less code, better quality.</string>
    <string name="description_368">A lightweight eventbus library for android, simplifies communication between Activities, Fragments, Threads, Services, etc.</string>
    <string name="description_369">A plugin for Android Studio and Intellij IDEA that speeds up your day to day android development.</string>
    <string name="description_370">Tinker is a hot-fix solution library for Android, it supports dex, library and resources update without reinstall apk.</string>
    <string name="description_371">Android executables browser</string>
    <string name="description_372">IntelliJ/AndroidStudio plugin which provides a button to connect your Android device over WiFi to install, run and debug your applications without a USB connected.</string>
    <string name="description_373">The ownCloud Android App</string>
    <string name="description_374">Memory safer implementation of android.os.Handler</string>
    <string name="description_375">Performance metrics library for Android development (includes dagger2metrics)</string>
    <string name="description_376">Android USB host serial driver library for CDC, FTDI, Arduino and other devices.</string>
    <string name="description_377">A sample project using Clean architecture and MVP in Android</string>
    <string name="description_378">Annotation Processor for setting arguments in android fragments.</string>
    <string name="description_379">Reasonable and elegant process of keeping alive</string>
    <string name="description_380">Android Shared preference wrapper than encrypts the values of Shared Preferences.</string>
    <string name="description_381">Based on the plug-in Android skinning framework to support the app and the external plug-in to provide resources for the skin solution, without restart Activity.</string>
    <string name="description_382">Android Debug Drawer for faster development</string>
    <string name="description_383">Android plugin development library (Frontia) and tech introductions, which means that you can upgrade your Android APP or fix emergent bugs, as well as reduce the file size of Apk without any re-installation.</string>
    <string name="description_384">A Job Queue specifically written for Android to easily schedule jobs (tasks) that run in the background, improving UX and application stability.</string>
    <string name="description_385">Android library that allows launching a custom activity when your app crashes, instead of showing the hated Unfortunately, X has stopped dialog.</string>
    <string name="description_386">A simple watchdog that detects Android ANR (Application Not Responding) error and throws a meaningful exception</string>
    <string name="description_387">Android library to handle jobs in the background.</string>
    <string name="description_388">[Deprecated] A backport of Android Lollipop\'s JobScheduler to api 10+</string>
    <string name="description_389">App is located in the foreground or background to determine the six methods</string>
    <string name="description_390">Java library to automate the analysis of Android heap dumps.</string>
    <string name="description_391">Get running processes on Android</string>
    <string name="description_392">A Java 8 Jar &amp; Android APK Reverse Engineering Suite (Decompiler, Editor, Debugger &amp; More)</string>
    <string name="description_393">A library that analyzes an Android device\'s specifications and calculates which year the device would be considered high end.</string>
    <string name="description_394">This is starter template for writing Android apps using Clean architecture</string>
    <string name="description_395">Separating data and state handling from Fragments or Activities without lots of boilerplate-code.</string>
    <string name="description_396">Memory safer implementation of android.os.Handler</string>
    <string name="description_397">Based on the Android system api package commonly used tools</string>
    <string name="description_398">a SharedPreferences replacement for Android with multiprocess support</string>
    <string name="description_399">screenshot-test-for-android is a library that can generate fast deterministic screenshots while running instrumentation tests in android.</string>
    <string name="description_400">A backport of the new Transitions API for Android</string>
    <string name="description_401">BLE Framework. Based on Bluetooth 4.0. Based on callback. Extremely simple! Communication with BluetoothLE(BLE) device as easy as HTTP communication.</string>
    <string name="description_402">The lib can make the ActivityOptions animations use in Android api3.1+</string>
    <string name="description_403">Android library to easily serialize and cache your objects to disk using key/value pairs.</string>
    <string name="description_404">A memory leak detection library for Android and Java.</string>
    <string name="description_405">Android developers should collect the following utils(updating)</string>
    <string name="description_406">The framework is different from androidannotations, Roboguice and other ioc framework, which is similar to a spring implementation.</string>
    <string name="description_407">c:geo - The powerful Android geocaching app.</string>
    <string name="description_408">Samples that use Google Play services (GoogleApiClient) and Location APIs to help you make your applications location aware.</string>
    <string name="description_409">Android library project that lets you manage the location updates to be as painless as possible</string>
    <string name="description_410">[DEPRECATED] Simple information balloon annotation for Android MapView</string>
    <string name="description_411">Android Scrolling Background Bitmap Example</string>
    <string name="description_412">This project allows you to calculate the route between two locations and displays it on a map.</string>
    <string name="description_413">Samples demonstrating how to use Google Maps Android API v2.</string>
    <string name="description_414">Handy extensions to the Google Maps Android API.</string>
    <string name="description_415">OpenStreetMap-Tools for Android</string>
    <string name="description_416">Type-safe HTTP client for Android and Java by Square, Inc.</string>
    <string name="description_417">An HTTP+HTTP/2 client for Android and Java applications.</string>
    <string name="description_418">An Asynchronous HTTP Library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_419">android orm, bitmap, http, view inject...</string>
    <string name="description_420">Asynchronous socket, http (client+server), websocket, and socket.io library for android. Based on nio, not threads.</string>
    <string name="description_421">A Complete Fast Android Networking Library that also support HTTP/2</string>
    <string name="description_422">Android library listening network connection state and Internet connectivity with RxJava Observables</string>
    <string name="description_423">LiteHttp is a simple, intelligent and flexible HTTP framework for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_424">Compact and easy to use, \'all-in-one\' android network solution</string>
    <string name="description_425">Remote Administration Tool for Android devices</string>
    <string name="description_426">Java HTTP Request Library</string>
    <string name="description_427">A light package for Android development, it handles loading image and network request.</string>
    <string name="description_428">Volley library : make everything faster . Its an improvements for Volley by Google for Android</string>
    <string name="description_429">Project with examples how to use the new Volley networking framework</string>
    <string name="description_430">ConnectBot is the first SSH client for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_431">AFWall+ (Android Firewall +) - iptables based firewall for Android</string>
    <string name="description_432">cSploit - The most complete and advanced IT security professional toolkit on Android.</string>
    <string name="description_433">An Android library that prevents your app from being pirated / cracked using Google Play Licensing (LVL), APK signature protection and more. API 8+ required.</string>
    <string name="description_434">An Android library containing a simple TableView and an advanced SortableTableView providing a lot of customisation possibilities to fit all needs.</string>
    <string name="description_435">Android point praise + 1 effect, support for text and images</string>
    <string name="description_436">A small, easy to use android library for implementing flipping between views as seen in the popular Flipboard application</string>
    <string name="description_437">Selector with wheel view, applicable to selecting money or other short length values.</string>
    <string name="description_438">A simple library to add carousel view in android app.</string>
    <string name="description_439">Android View that displays different content based on its state</string>
    <string name="description_440">CreditCardView is an Android library that allows developers to create the UI which replicates an actual Credit Card.</string>
    <string name="description_441">Android Countdown View</string>
    <string name="description_442">A new canvas drawing library for Android. Aims to be the Fabric.js for Android. Supports text, images, and hand/stylus drawing input.The library has a website and API docs, check it out http://antwankakki.github.io/FabricView/</string>
    <string name="description_443">A Simple Android LabelView.</string>
    <string name="description_444">A TagView library for Android. Customize your own &amp; Drag effect.</string>
    <string name="description_445">An Android TagView Widget. You can edit the tag\'s style, and set listener of selecting or deleting tag.</string>
    <string name="description_446">An Android Library to help you create actionbar tabs like\'Capitaine train\' app by Cyril Mottier</string>
    <string name="description_447">Customizable, sensor-enabled, door sign custom views for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_448">Android badge control</string>
    <string name="description_449">A horizontal view scroller library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_450">AndroidTreeView. TreeView implementation for android</string>
    <string name="description_451">A Material Design themed ShowcaseView for Android</string>
    <string name="description_452">An android password view that looks like the pay password view in wechat app and alipay app.</string>
    <string name="description_453">A Material Android password view that toggles password visibility via an eye icon.</string>
    <string name="description_454">Android 3D Stereo Unlimited Rotating Container. This is a stereo view (3D) for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_455">Android Scroll to select controls</string>
    <string name="description_456">An Android Widget for selecting items that rotate on a wheel.</string>
    <string name="description_457">RoundedLetterView like the one in Android 5.0 Contacts app</string>
    <string name="description_458">Android Quilt View Library</string>
    <string name="description_459">Android Timeline View is used to display views like Tracking of shipment/order, steppers etc.</string>
    <string name="description_460">Cute timeline view for android</string>
    <string name="description_461">An Android library introducing a stack of Views with the first item being flippable.</string>
    <string name="description_462">FogView is a android library that can show fog on any layout and the fog removes when user rubs it.</string>
    <string name="description_463">A library for displaying math formula in Android apps.</string>
    <string name="description_464">SpiderWebScoreView is a spider WebScoreView for Android. Android is used on a cobweb score view</string>
    <string name="description_465">SweetAlert for Android, a beautiful and clever alert dialog</string>
    <string name="description_466">Advanced dialog solution for android</string>
    <string name="description_467">A simple, powerful campaign widget control</string>
    <string name="description_468">An Android Dialog Lib simplify customization.</string>
    <string name="description_469">A sample that demonstrates to use registered fingerprints to authenticate the user in your app</string>
    <string name="description_470">A small library replicating the new dialogs in android L.</string>
    <string name="description_471">Android AlertDialog with mowing dots progress indicator</string>
    <string name="description_472">Fab and Dialog Morphing Animation on Android</string>
    <string name="description_473">A custom CheckBox with animation for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_474">AlertViewController imitation iOS</string>
    <string name="description_475">NewQuickAction is a small android library to create QuickAction dialog.</string>
    <string name="description_476">A util for setting status bar style on Android App.</string>
    <string name="description_477">Tidy up your Android status bar before taking screenshots for the Play Store.</string>
    <string name="description_478">On the importance of taste</string>
    <string name="description_479">[DEPRECATED] Apply background tinting to the Android system UI when using KitKat translucent modes</string>
    <string name="description_480">Ultra Pull to Refresh for Android. Support all the views.</string>
    <string name="description_481">This component like SwipeRefreshLayout, it is more beautiful than SwipeRefreshLayout.</string>
    <string name="description_482">This is a drop-down control, it is more beautiful and powerful than SwipeRefreshLayout</string>
    <string name="description_483">Android widget with pull to refresh for all the views,and support loadMore for ListView , RecyclerView, GridView and SwipeRefreshLayout.</string>
    <string name="description_484">Performance comparison of android pull to refresh repos in github.</string>
    <string name="description_485">According to Maxwin\'s XListView transformation, perfect pull-down refresh to load more features and achieve automatic refresh and automatic loading and other functions, and increase support for ScrollView.</string>
    <string name="description_486">DEPRECATED This project aims to provide a reusable Pull to Refresh widget for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_487">[DEPRECATED] Android Library that implements Snackbars from Google\'s Material Design documentation.</string>
    <string name="description_488">In-layout notifications. Based on Toast notifications and article by Cyril Mottier</string>
    <string name="description_489">Make your native android Toasts Tasty</string>
    <string name="description_490">Demonstrate how UC browser display a system overlay view in any platform above API level 9.</string>
    <string name="description_491">An Android Toast replacement, similar to the one seen in the GMail app.</string>
    <string name="description_492">Create Toast like tooltips, but targets can be specified, plus custom properties and features</string>
    <string name="description_493">The Most Powerful Swipe Layout!</string>
    <string name="description_494">An easy to use swiping-view for Android</string>
    <string name="description_495">Android swipe-to-dismiss mini-library and sample code</string>
    <string name="description_496">Android library which allows you to swipe down from an activity to close it.</string>
    <string name="description_497">This repository hosts a library that provides an easy way to include an autonomous layer/view that slides from any side of your screen</string>
    <string name="description_498">SwipeBack is an android library that can finish a activity by using gesture.</string>
    <string name="description_499">A nicer-looking, more intuitive and highly customizable alternative for radio buttons and dropdowns for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_500">A Tinder-like Android library to create the swipe cards effect. You can swipe left or right to like or dislike the content.</string>
    <string name="description_501">A simple, customizable and easy to use swipeable view stack for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_502">A Tinder style Swipeable deck view for Android</string>
    <string name="description_503">SwipeBack for Android Activities to do pretty the same as the android back-button will do, but in a really intuitive way by using a swipe gesture</string>
    <string name="description_504">Context sensitive notifications for Android</string>
    <string name="description_505">effects for android notifications</string>
    <string name="description_506">A example of an android app that receives push notifications using MQTT.</string>
    <string name="description_507">Open Source Project to the Provide AN PUSH the Notification Support for the Android - A XMPP based the Notification Server and Client A Tool Kit.</string>
    <string name="description_508">AcDisplay is a new way of handling notifications in Android.</string>
    <string name="description_509">A powerful library for creating notifications in android platform.</string>
    <string name="description_510">An Android template with navigation drawer for material design</string>
    <string name="description_511">Android drawer icon with material design animation</string>
    <string name="description_512">Side menu for android applications</string>
    <string name="description_513">Navigation menu for Android (based off Google+ app)</string>
    <string name="description_514">Floating Action Button for Android based on Material Design specification</string>
    <string name="description_515">[DEPRECATED] Android floating action button</string>
    <string name="description_516">Android Floating ActionButton with a progress indicator ring</string>
    <string name="description_517">Support Floating Action Button transformation for Android</string>
    <string name="description_518">Circle button widget for Android</string>
    <string name="description_519">Icons, Borders, Radius ... for Android buttons</string>
    <string name="description_520">FButton - a flat button library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_521">ExpandableSelector is an Android library created to show a list of Button/ImageButton widgets inside a animated container which can be collapsed or expanded.</string>
    <string name="description_522">Android library to create buttons with Twitter\'s heart like animation.</string>
    <string name="description_523">Android Circular Progress Button</string>
    <string name="description_524">This is a UI lib for Android. Effects like shining.</string>
    <string name="description_525">Twitter\'s heart animation for Android</string>
    <string name="description_526">A very simple arc layout library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_527">A small Android library allowing you to have a smooth and customizable horizontal indeterminate ProgressBar.</string>
    <string name="description_528">A beautiful, slim Android ProgressBar.</string>
    <string name="description_529">Android library to display progress like google does in some of his services.</string>
    <string name="description_530">An android library to display a progressbar that goes around an image.</string>
    <string name="description_531">DownloadProgressBar is an android library that delivers awesome custom progress bar. You can manipulate it\'s state in every way.</string>
    <string name="description_532">A DownloadProgressButton with Animation for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_533">Round Corner Progress Bar Library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_534">HoloCircularProgressBar is a Custom View implementation for Android you might know from the Android Clock App from Android 4.1</string>
    <string name="description_535">Animated circular progress view for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_536">Material style circular progress bar for Android</string>
    <string name="description_537">A circle progress animation view on Android</string>
    <string name="description_538">Android fillable progress view working with SVG paths. This is a nice option too if you want to create an interesting branding logo for your app.</string>
    <string name="description_539">a simple loadingview for android with animation.</string>
    <string name="description_540">High imitates the new version 58 to load the animation.</string>
    <string name="description_541">Android loading view</string>
    <string name="description_542">Android CatLoadingView</string>
    <string name="description_543">An Android library providing to realize wave loading effect.</string>
    <string name="description_544">A wave view of android,can be used as progress bar.</string>
    <string name="description_545">waveview for android</string>
    <string name="description_546">Implementation of the fragment with the ability to display indeterminate progress indicator when you are waiting for the initial data.</string>
    <string name="description_547">custom progress layout view for Android</string>
    <string name="description_548">An implement of ProgressHUD for Android, similar to MBProgressHUD, SVProgressHUD for iOS.</string>
    <string name="description_549">Circular SeekBar view for Android</string>
    <string name="description_550">A progress wheel for android, intended for use instead of the standard progress bar.</string>
    <string name="description_551">Standalone Android widget for picking a single date from a calendar view.</string>
    <string name="description_552">Useful and powerful date picker for android</string>
    <string name="description_553">A combined DatePicker and TimePicker in a DialogFragment for Android</string>
    <string name="description_554">An Android time picker library.</string>
    <string name="description_555">Third-party date and time pickers for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_556">Pick a date or time on Android in style</string>
    <string name="description_557">A material-styled android view that provisions picking of a date, time &amp; recurrence option, all from a single user-interface.</string>
    <string name="description_558">A better calendar for Android</string>
    <string name="description_559">A simple example of a responsive Month Calendar app widget for Android</string>
    <string name="description_560">An Android project providing easy navigation between a calendar and an agenda. This library replicates the basic features from the Sunrise Calendar (now Outlook) app, coupled with some small design touch from the Google Calendar app.</string>
    <string name="description_561">An android library which provides a compact calendar view much like the one used in google calenders.</string>
    <string name="description_562">Simple and fantastic wheel view in realistic effect for android.</string>
    <string name="description_563">A backport of the Android 4.2 NumberPicker</string>
    <string name="description_564">Another NumberPicker with more flexible attributes on Android platform</string>
    <string name="description_565">Android library to display a list of items for pick one</string>
    <string name="description_566">Photopicker and document picker for android</string>
    <string name="description_567">Andrews selector class library, including date selector, time selector, single selector, city address selector, license plate number selector, digital selector, constellation selector, zodiac selector, color selector, file selector, directory Selectors, etc.</string>
    <string name="description_568">Android library that provides a file explorer to let users select files on external storage.</string>
    <string name="description_569">Android File Grouping Plugin</string>
    <string name="description_570">A TextView that automatically resizes text to fit perfectly within its bounds.</string>
    <string name="description_571">An Android text view with scrolling text change animation</string>
    <string name="description_572">Android\'s TextView that can expand/collapse like the Google Play\'s app description</string>
    <string name="description_573">(DEPRECATED) Android experiment showing a sinking TextView</string>
    <string name="description_574">Android Text Full Jusiftication / Wrapping / Justify / Hyphenate - V2.0</string>
    <string name="description_575">Insanely easy way to define clickable links within a TextView.</string>
    <string name="description_576">Android slanted TextView .</string>
    <string name="description_577">Android platform under the rich text parser, support Html and Markdown.</string>
    <string name="description_578">Advanced Android TextView</string>
    <string name="description_579">a super textview for android</string>
    <string name="description_580">Android Bubble View</string>
    <string name="description_581">Support for Android graphics mixed text, text and other effects around the picture</string>
    <string name="description_582">Knife is a rich text editor component for writing documents in Android.</string>
    <string name="description_583">Android form edit text is an extension of EditText that brings data validation facilities to the edittext.</string>
    <string name="description_584">Android validation library which helps developer boil down the tedious work to three easy steps.</string>
    <string name="description_585">Gmail style MultiAutoCompleteTextView for Android</string>
    <string name="description_586">Software keyboard open/close watcher for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_587">android emoticonsKeyboard support emoji and user-defined emoticon. easy to integrated into your project</string>
    <string name="description_588">rich text editor which enables users to insert/delete bitmaps and text into edit-view with animations.</string>
    <string name="description_589">Android Markdown</string>
    <string name="description_590">Show/Hide Password EditText is a very simple extension of Android\'s EditText that puts a clickable hide/show icon in the right hand side of the EditText that allows showing of the password.</string>
    <string name="description_591">RichEditor for Android is a beautiful Rich Text WYSIWYG Editor for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_592">UI form validation library for Android</string>
    <string name="description_593">Custom fonts in Android the easy way...</string>
    <string name="description_594">Implementation of a TextView and all its direct/indirect subclasses with native support for the Roboto fonts, includes the brand new Roboto Slab fonts.</string>
    <string name="description_595">Exploring possible implementations for better underline text decoration on Android</string>
    <string name="description_596">Typeface helper for Android</string>
    <string name="description_597">A library to show emoji in TextView, EditText (like WhatsApp) for Android</string>
    <string name="description_598">Android chat interface + emoji expression + expression to achieve large.</string>
    <string name="description_599">One line of code to implement emoji to your whole android application.</string>
    <string name="description_600">Fast Record,Organize,and Share. The android memo app you will deeply love. ❤</string>
    <string name="description_601">Open source note-taking application for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_602">A powerful Android chart view / graph view library, supporting line- bar- pie- radar- bubble- and candlestick charts as well as scaling, dragging and animations.</string>
    <string name="description_603">Charts/graphs library for Android compatible with API 8+, several chart types with support for scaling, scrolling and animations</string>
    <string name="description_604">Android library to create charts.</string>
    <string name="description_605">Android Graph Library for creating zoomable and scrollable line and bar graphs.</string>
    <string name="description_606">An Android chart and graph library.</string>
    <string name="description_607">An easy-to-use Android charts library with animation.</string>
    <string name="description_608">DecoView: Android arc based animated charting library.</string>
    <string name="description_609">A simple Android sparkline chart view.</string>
    <string name="description_610">Fit Chart is an Android view similar to Google Fit wheel chart.</string>
    <string name="description_611">[UNMAINTAINED] A library that helps developers creating their Android Application with Material Design.</string>
    <string name="description_612">Material Design Search Bar for Android</string>
    <string name="description_613">Android Search View based on Material design guidelines.</string>
    <string name="description_614">Simple, pretty and powerful logger for android</string>
    <string name="description_615">A logger with a small, extensible API which provides utility on top of Android\'s normal Log class.</string>
    <string name="description_616">Stetho is a debug bridge for Android applications, enabling the powerful Chrome Developer Tools and much more.</string>
    <string name="description_617">Lightweight GPS Logging Application For Android. Available on the Android Market as \'GPSLogger for Android\'</string>
    <string name="description_618">A tool for reverse engineering Android apk files</string>
    <string name="description_619">Application Crash Reports for Android</string>
    <string name="description_620">proguard resource for Android by wechat team</string>
    <string name="description_621">Tools to work with android .dex and java .class files</string>
    <string name="description_622">A utility library for your daily Android needs</string>
    <string name="description_623">Android Library to help you with your runtime Permissions.</string>
    <string name="description_624">This sample shows runtime permissions available in Android M and above.</string>
    <string name="description_625">It contains most of the Android utility classes.</string>
    <string name="description_626">General purpose utilities and hash functions for Android and Java (aka java-common)</string>
    <string name="description_627">Context free and basic utils to build Android project conveniently</string>
    <string name="description_628">Android Library to display your changelog</string>
    <string name="description_629">Bind Android views and callbacks to fields and methods.</string>
    <string name="description_630">Used to integrate Android apps with Facebook Platform.https://developers.facebook.com/docs/android</string>
    <string name="description_631">Library for easy work with Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn and Google on Android</string>
    <string name="description_632">Crowdfunding app concept for Android. Created to showcase new trends in Android development with strong focus on Material Design.</string>
    <string name="description_633">Firebase Quickstart Samples for Android https://firebase.google.com</string>
    <string name="description_634">UI bindings for Firebase</string>
    <string name="description_635">Bubbles for Android is an Android library to provide chat heads capabilities on your apps. With a fast way to integrate with your development.</string>
    <string name="description_636">Accept PayPal and credit cards in your Android app</string>
    <string name="description_637">A lightweight implementation of Android In-app Billing Version 3</string>
    <string name="description_638">Library for Android In-App Billing (Version 3)</string>
    <string name="description_639">Android Market In-app Billing Library</string>
    <string name="description_640">A Material design Android pincode library. Supports Fingerprint.</string>
    <string name="description_641">Simply Implement Dribbble\'s popular shot</string>
    <string name="description_642">A beautiful gift Cards for android</string>
    <string name="description_643">Gesture detector framework for multitouch handling on Android, based on Android\'s ScaleGestureDetector.http://code.almeros.com/android-multitouch-gesture-detectors</string>
    <string name="description_644">Read data from public transit cards using your NFC Android phone! http://codebutler.github.com/farebot</string>
    <string name="description_645">Bitcoin Wallet app for your Android device. Standalone Bitcoin node, no centralized backend required.</string>
    <string name="description_646">Wrapper of syncthing for Android. https://syncthing.net/</string>
    <string name="description_647">CastCompanionLibrary-android is a library project to enable developers integrate Cast capabilities into their applications faster and easier.</string>
    <string name="description_648">A multicard menu that can open and close with animation on android</string>
    <string name="description_649">This library offers a simple method to add a small badge icon to your ActionBar-MenuItem</string>
    <string name="description_650">Android Wheel Picker.</string>
    <string name="description_651">Astrid: Android\'s #1 Task Management Application http://www.astrid.com</string>
    <string name="description_652">A lightweight Youtube frontend for Android.</string>
    <string name="description_653">An android library for displaying fps from the choreographer and percentage of time with two or more frames dropped</string>
    <string name="description_654">Android library that implements a table with fixed headers.</string>
    <string name="description_655">SlidingDeck View for Android</string>
    <string name="description_656">Steppers view library for Android, based on Google Material design guidelines</string>
    <string name="description_657">Custom ViewGroup implementation of the circular rotation menu, support to follow the finger rotation and rapid rotation.</string>
    <string name="description_658">Android version of the waterfall layout</string>
    <string name="description_659">Flexbox for Android</string>
    <string name="description_660">A powerful Android layout view that use java expression in layout params to describe relative positions.</string>
    <string name="description_661">Simple material-style flyout menus for Android. There are many flyout type menus for Android, but this one is mine.</string>
    <string name="description_662">Android widgets to implement folding animation</string>
    <string name="description_663">Imitation UC weather drop-down and WeChat drop-down eyes</string>
    <string name="description_664">An android library that brings the expandable layout with various animation. You can include optional contents and use everywhere.</string>
    <string name="description_665">Explorations around Android custom layouts</string>
    <string name="description_666">Android Shadow Layout</string>
    <string name="description_667">Android implementation of FlowLayout. Layout arranges its children in multiple rows depending on their width.</string>
    <string name="description_668">Android layout which supports expanding and collapsing child views</string>
    <string name="description_669">An android library for navigator that stick on the top</string>
    <string name="description_670">Android device shake detection.</string>
    <string name="description_671">Android widget for selecting a range of values.</string>
    <string name="description_672">a PaperShredder view for android</string>
    <string name="description_673">Android Weather Library: android weather lib to develop weather based app fast and easily.http://survivingwithandroid.github.io/WeatherLib/</string>
    <string name="description_674">Android Library that implements Snackbars (former known as Undobar) from Google\'s Material Design documentation. http://soarcn.github.io/UndoBar</string>
    <string name="description_675">[DEPRECATED] An implementation of Android\'s Undo Bar as seen in Google\'s Gmail app.</string>
    <string name="description_676">Fast and low memory usage of Chinese to Pinyin library for Java and Android.</string>
    <string name="description_677">A cool Open Source CoverFlow view for Android with several fancy effects. http://davidschreiber.github.io/FancyCoverFlow/</string>
    <string name="description_678">A custom Android View for drawing smooth signatures</string>
    <string name="description_679">Google Santa Tracker app for Android is an educational and entertaining tradition that brings joy to millions of children (and children at heart) across the world over the December holiday period.</string>
    <string name="description_680">an animated circular menu for Android</string>
    <string name="description_681">Side menu with some categories to choose. https://yalantis.com</string>
    <string name="description_682">A menu which can ... BOOM! - Android</string>
    <string name="description_683">An Android library that allows you to easily create applications with slide-in menus. You may use it in your Android apps provided that you cite this project and include the license in your app. Thanks!</string>
    <string name="description_684">This library provides a simple way to add a draggable sliding up panel (popularized by Google Music and Google Maps) to your Android application. Brought to you by Umano. http://umano.me</string>
    <string name="description_685">Android Satellite Menu</string>
    <string name="description_686">AIMSICD • Fight IMSI-Catcher, StingRay and silent SMS!</string>
    <string name="description_687">The most beautiful SMS messenger app for Android</string>
    <string name="description_688">Backup Android SMS, MMS and call log to Gmail / Gcal / IMAP</string>
    <string name="description_689">Sample code for the Android Mobile Vision API. https://developers.google.com/vision/</string>
    <string name="description_690">Router activities and methods with url for android</string>
    <string name="description_691">A hotfix library for Android platform, and not just this...</string>
    <string name="description_692">Android framework for node.js applications</string>
    <string name="description_693">LightCycle lets self-contained classes respond to Android’s lifecycle events http://soundcloud.github.io/lightcycle/</string>
    <string name="description_694">Easily upload files (FTP / Multipart / Binary) in the background with progress indication notification</string>
    <string name="description_695">Light weight and simple Multi-Thread Downloader for Android</string>
    <string name="description_696">Android/Java download manager library help you to download files in parallel mechanism in some chunks.</string>
    <string name="description_697">To download files and to avoid using DOWNLOAD_WITHOUT_NOTIFICATION permission if you are using Android\'s DownloadManager in your apps.</string>
    <string name="description_698">Face-to-face file transfer, Android-side Smart fast transfer, Andrews each other files, LAN, no network transfer files, Android, file transfer</string>
    <string name="description_699">Google Guice on Android, version 3.0 [RETIRED]</string>
    <string name="description_700">A fast dependency injector for Android and Java. http://square.github.io/dagger/</string>
    <string name="description_701">Desktop/Android/HTML5/iOS Java game development framework</string>
    <string name="description_702">Free Android 2D OpenGL Game Engine</string>
    <string name="description_703">Android filters based on OpenGL (idea from GPUImage for iOS)</string>
    <string name="description_704">An easy open source Android Native Game FrameWork.</string>
    <string name="description_705">A native Android client to map the Pokemon around you!</string>
    <string name="description_706">The android port of the 2048 game (for offline playing)</string>

</resources>
